In Please Please Please Please Please
二零二二年广东省初中学业水平考试
英语试卷听力部分。
首先播放两分钟的音乐信号，请监考老师调试好播音设备的音量。
音。
月结束后，听力考试正式开始
嗯。
Please adjust the Please
Please adjust the equipment.
equipment. Please Please Please Please Please adjust the equipment.
Please adjust volume the adjust the
adjust Please adjust volume equipment.
视听到此结束。
equipment. a. 1.
一，听说应用。
听句子。
请根据所听内容选择符合题意的图画，回答问题，
并将答题卡上对应题目所选的选项涂黑。
每个句子听两遍。
听每小题之前，你有五秒钟的时间。
阅读题目。
每小题听完后，你有五秒钟的答题时间。
The little girl drew a picture of two apples.
The drew two 2.
The sign says, Picking flowers is not allowed here.
sign says, Picking flowers is not allowed here.
3. I spent the whole morning playing football.
I spent the whole morning playing I spent morning
4. The girl is putting a hat on the snowman.
The girl is putting a hat on the snowman.
5. I get up at 7 on weekdays and at 8.30 on weekends.
5. get up at 7 on weekdays and at 8.30 on weekends.
get up weekdays.30 weekends.
b. After After listening question, question.
听对话，请根据每段对话的内容回答问题。
从每小题所给的。三个选项中选出一个最佳答案，
并将答题卡上对应题目所选的选项涂黑。
每段对话听两遍。
听每小题之前，你有五秒钟的时间阅读题目。
每小题。
听完后，你有五秒钟的答题时间。
听第一段对话，回答第六小题。
question. b. Listen
听第二段对话，回答。
the b. I wasn't at home when it happened.
第七小题：
听第三段对话，回答第八小题。
听第。
四段对话，回答第九小题。
听第五段对话，回答第十小题。
b. Listen wrong with your computer?
听第六段对话，回答第十一至十二。
I don't know.
It wouldn't start.
Let me have a look.
Maybe I can fix it.
Thank you. It's very nice of you.
Lily, can I use your computer for a while?
Sure. What's wrong with your computer?
I don't know.
It wouldn't start.
Let me have a look.
Maybe I can fix it.
Thank you. It's very nice of you.
b. b. conversation.
听第七段对话，回答第十三至十五小题。
Please answer the eleventh
c. j. Jason got into the habit of reading when he was a little boy.
听短文，请根据所听内容，从每小题所给的三个选项中。
选出一个最佳答案，并将答题卡上对应题目所选的选项涂黑。
短文听两遍。
听短文之前，你有二十五秒钟的时间阅读题目。
听完后，你有二十五秒。
中的答题时间。
j. mother used to read bedtime stories to him every night.
Unluckily, at the age of 12, he dropped out of because his family was so poor.
But this never stopped him from reading.
Later, Jason got the job of driving the rubbish truck.
One night, he found some books left by the road.
They were thrown away as rubbish.
Jason felt so sad about this.
He decided to save such books.
Over the years, he has collected about 20,000 books.
With so many books, he turned his home into a small library for children.
The library opens every weekend.
Children can have a wonderful reading time there, and they all love this place.
Jason got into the habit of reading when he was a little boy.
His mother used to read bedtime stories to him every night.
Unluckily, at the age of 12,
he dropped out of because his family was so poor.
But this never stopped him from reading.
Later, Jason got the job of driving the rubbish truck.
One night, he found some books left by the road.
They were thrown away as rubbish.
Jason felt so sad about this.
He decided to save such books.
Over the years, he has collected about 20,000 books.
With so many books, he turned his home into a small library for children.
The library opens every weekend.
Children can have a wonderful reading time there, and they all love this place.
D. Hi, everyone.
听填信息。
你将听到一则设计活动的介绍，请根据所听内容填写下面的信息卡。
并将答案写在答题卡对应题目的答题位置上。
短文听两遍。
听短文之前，你有二十五秒钟的时间阅读题目。
听完后，你有二十五秒钟的答题时间。
I'm glad to tell you that the famous magazine Environment wants good designs of T
-shirts from students in art schools like ours.
The topic is about saving the panda.
You're all welcome to take part in this activity.
Please make sure to put the picture and some words on the T -shirt to show that you
care about the panda.
Your works must be handed in before July 21.
The result will come out on August 11.
The winners will get the chance to work with the magazine next winter holiday.
The winners' will get 100 green T -shirts for free.
It is a good chance.
If you want to join in, please get ready.
Good luck to you all.
Hi, everyone. I'm glad to tell you that the famous magazine Environment wants good
designs of T -shirts from students in art schools like ours.
The topic is about saving the panda.
You're all welcome to take part in this activity.
Please make sure to put the picture and some words on the T -shirt to show that you
care about the panda.
Your works must be handed in before July 21.
The result will come out on August 11.
The winners will get the chance to work with the magazine next winter holiday.
The winners' will get 100 green T for free.
It is a good chance.
If you want to join in, please get ready.
Good luck to you all.
听力理解部分到此结束